I'm sure most of us enjoy going on holiday.
我相信我们大多数人都喜欢去度假。
It's a break from the routine and a chance to jet off somewhere with friends or family.
度假可以逃离乏味的日常生活，也是一个与朋友或家人乘飞机去某个地方的机会。
This might involve sightseeing and soaking up local culture in a new destination, or it could be kicking back and lazing by a pool or on a beach.
度假可能包括观光，在异地沉浸于当地文化，也可能是放松身心，在泳池边或海滩上慵懒地躺着。
But, whatever we choose, the most convenient way to do it is on a package holiday.
但是，无论我们选择什么，最方便的方式就是参加全包旅游。
This type of vacation combines the flight, accommodation, transfers and sometimes the services of a rep, all into one booking.
这种度假方式将航班、住宿、交通接送，有时还包括驻点代表的服务，整合到一个预约中。
They were traditionally sold by travel agents on the high street, but as a few big-brand names closed, many are now purchased on websites.
传统上，它们由商业街上的旅行社出售，但随着一些大品牌关闭，现在许多都是在网站上购买的。
Travel journalist Simon Calder explains that the benefits of a proper package holiday are that "by booking flights and accommodation in a single transaction from a tour operator, you transfer all the risk to the company."
旅游记者西蒙·卡尔德解释说，一个真正的套餐度假的好处在于，"通过向旅游运营商一次性预订航班和住宿，你将所有风险转移给了公司。"
This means it has to sort things out when things go wrong, and if the operator goes bust, you can get a refund.
这意味着当出现问题时运营商必须解决，如果它破产，你可以获得退款。
This protection can give you peace of mind, but there are other benefits too.
这种保护能让你安心，但还有其他好处。
A package holiday can also be great value.
全包旅游还可能非常划算。
A tour company can book airplane seats and hotel rooms in bulk which means that they can negotiate better discounts for its holidaymakers.
旅游公司可以批量预订机票和酒店房间，这意味着他们可以为度假者争取到更好的折扣。
There are often deals on food and drink too, with some companies offering all-inclusive packages – although, this can discourage someone from eating outside the hotel and sampling local cuisine and helping the local economy.
通常还会有餐饮优惠，一些公司提供一价全包的套餐——尽管这可能会阻止人们在酒店外用餐，品尝当地美食，并帮助当地经济。
But with no-frills airlines offering cheap flights and websites offering cheap hotel accommodation, some of us have been tempted to be independent travellers or backpackers.
但随着廉价航空公司提供便宜机票，网站提供廉价酒店住宿，我们中的一些人被吸引成为独立旅行者或背包客。
While that might suit some, the package holiday offering has evolved, and, in the UK, for example, travel experts say the package holiday is growing in popularity, particularly among younger travellers.
虽然这可能适合一些人，但套餐度假的产品已经演变，例如在英国，旅游专家表示全包度假越来越受欢迎，尤其是在年轻旅行者中。
The Association of British Travel Agents told the BBC "there is a greater emphasis on personalisation, where holidaymakers can mix and match what they want to include instead of purchasing a pre-defined package."
英国旅行社协会告诉BBC，"现在更加注重个性化，度假者可以混搭他们想要包含的项目，而不是购买预先定义的套餐。"
The only problem is deciding where to go!
唯一的问题就是决定去哪里！